<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DangerMoleMobile</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="take_pic">Snap</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">DangerMole</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">(example username)</string>
    <string name="nav_header_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="full_disclaimer">This app is intended for entertainment and educational purposes only and should not be
        used in place of a Doctor\'s advice or in lieu of medical attention.
    </string>
    <string name="about_us_text">
        \tDanger Mole is an app conceived and developed by MSU Denver students as a solution to early detection of melanoma in nevi (moles).
        Danger Mole is designed to run on android and makes use of TensorFlow’s powerful machine learning libraries.
        \n\n
        \tThe model itself is trained on data acquired from the International Skin Imaging Collaboration (ISIC) database linked below.
        Our team is composed of four undergraduates in pursuit of a BS in computer science.
        \n\n
        \tThe project is currently in development as of spring 2019 and is intended as a prototype and not a definitive medical resource.</string>
    <string name="general_info_text">
        \tMelanocytic Nevi are a subcategory of Melanocytic Tumors containing nevus cells.
        \nWhile the majority of moles are benign, it is important to regularly check your moles for changes in shape,
        texture, symmetry and color as these are signs of melanoma. Danger Mole uses these metrics to gauge the
        overall health of the mole by analyzing it against a trained neural network using TensorFlow’s framework.
        \n\n\tFurther resources on melanoma can be found at cancer.gov:</string>
    <string name="link_skin">
        <a href="https://www.cancer.gov/types/skin">Official resource on skin cancer</a> </string>
    <string name="link_ISIC">
        <a href= "https://www.isic-archive.com/#!/topWithHeader/wideContentTop/main">Isic website</a></string>
    <string name="git_dangermole">
        <a href="https://github.com/greengroupmsudenver/DangerMole">Our Github</a></string>
    <string name="file_creation_error_msg">Needs camera and storage permissions.</string>
    <string name="link_symptoms">
        <a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/melanoma-skin-cancer/detection-diagnosis-staging/signs-and-symptoms.html">Melanoma symptoms: healthy vs unhealthy moles</a> </string>
</resources>
